Joseph: King of Dreams is a family, animation,
drama film directed by Rob LaDuca.
In this animated retelling of the story from the Bible's Book of Genesis, Joseph's gift of dream
interpretation and his brilliantly colored coat inspires jealousy in his brothers.
Joseph (voice), played by Ben Affleck.
Judah (voice), played by Mark Hamill.
Jacob (voice), played by Richard Herd.
Rachel (voice), played by Maureen McGovern.
Asenath (voice), played by Jodi Benson.
Zuleika (voice), played by Judith Light.
Joseph Williams (born September 1, 1960) is an American singer, songwriter and film score composer, best
known as the lead vocalist of the rock band Toto from 1986 to 1988 and again since 2010.
Outside of Toto, he has worked as a composer and studio vocalist, including providing
the singing voice of Simba in the 1994 animated film The Lion King.
The film explores themes of faith, bible, ancient egypt, christian film.
The tone is emotional.